inv.bz 2014-02-09

# inv.bz

### Privacy Policy 

By using this website, you consent to the terms of our Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to change, modify, add or remove portions from this Privacy Policy at any time. Amendments to the Privacy Policy will become effective when posted on the website. We will not provide you with separate notice of any change in our Privacy Policy. Your continued use of our website following the posting of changes to these terms means you accept these changes. 

Inv Global ltd is committed to keeping the personal information collected about our potential, current and former clients confidential and secure in compliance with the laws of the Republic of Panama. 

We respects each individuals right to privacy. We value our relationship with you, and we take pride in maintaining loyalty and respect with each individual client by providing you with security. 

Some of our site pages may utilize "cookies" or other tracking technologies. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our website is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our website and your web experience. 

Our website may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of these websites. 

Due to its financial nature, the Inv Global ltd website is not designed to appeal to children. Accordingly, we do not intend to collect personal information from anyone we know to be under 18 years of age. 

Under no circumstances will Inv Global ltd share information about you with other companies, affiliates or partners and we will comply with confidentiality standards. We do not sell information about you to anyone.
